{
    "id": "4e319d96550d4c16a66a4695b7a2e884",
    "title": "Nouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Where is your ......................................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "luggage",
                "luggages"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5d5c1aeff8c741d7b5ff4b38c3e232cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like to paint the ........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "scenery",
                "sceneries"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "458094b0c8dd4364835cbdd2b8173fec"
        },
        {
            "question": "She gave me some ........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "advice",
                "advices"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "666a47cf4a3e4704aac3427fb29c6179"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has eaten two .............................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "loaves of bread",
                "breads"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0f7378c512244fde80c36cdae3379c0d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ............................................... important work to do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "an",
                "some"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0b5c83b5075b4d5bb225979eb7fa5b94"
        },
        {
            "question": "......................................... lightning struck the building.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "A",
                "A flash of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1dff7dcc90154cde9ad509fcffbab9cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The lightning was followed by a deafening ..........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "clap of thunder",
                "thunder"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "738eb0dd9c61414a8f1c721a7b04f48e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I heard ..............................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a news",
                "a piece of news"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3d2b4a7dccef40a59c87d2d4bbb20a99"
        },
        {
            "question": "We need to buy ............................................. furniture.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "some"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9b54c145a4b54464ab9ce38f9e7ff14f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you got ......................................... equipment to fix this?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "an",
                "some"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a4b7f2fdda7a4229b0987044e7479a1d"
        }
    ]
}